Emmet Family
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Printed Material, 1872-1989, undated, Series 10:; (boxes 8 and sol 11, 0.4 linear ft.)
  - Exhibition announcement and catalogs for Wilfrid De Glehn (see also sol 11), 1978-1989 (Box 8, Reel 4766)
  - Exhibition catalogs for various members of the Emmet family, 1936-1970 (Box 8, Reel 4766)
  - Reproductions of art work by various members of the Emmet family (see also sol 11), undated, (4 folders) (Box 8, Reel 4766)
  - Book, Out of Town, written and illustrated by Rosina Emmet Sherwood (the book has not been microfilmed), 1896 (Box 8, Reel 4766)
- Photographs, 1875-1944, undated, Series 11:; (boxes 9, 10, sol 11, 1.2 linear ft.)
  The files are arranged chronologically and contain photographs of Emmet family members, their friends, colleagues, and works of art.
  - Photographs of Julia Colt Pierson Emmet, William Jenkins Emmet and miscellaneous family members, 1875-1944, undated (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Tintypes of Bay (Ellen), Jane, and Lydia Emmet in Paris, undated (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of Jane and Lydia Emmet in Paris, undated (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of Rosina Emmet Sherwood, 1877, undated, (2 folders) (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of Rosina Emmet Sherwood, Robert Temple Emmet, and the Sherwood home "Skene Wood," 1929-1944, undated (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photograph of Robert Emmet Sherwood, circa 1909 (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of Lydia Field Emmet, 1925-1932, undated, (4 folders) (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of Jane Erin Emmet De Glehn and Wilfrid De Glehn, 1875-1930s, (3 folders) (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photograph of Richard Harding Davis, undated (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of Frederick MacMonnies and his art class, undated (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of Augustus Saint-Gaudens, undated (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of unidentified individuals, undated (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Installation photographs from the Arden Galleries exhibition, 1936 (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of art works by Julia Colt Pierson Emmet, undated (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of art works by Rosina Emmet Sherwood (see also sol 11), (7 folders) (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of art works by Lydia Field Emmet (see also sol 11), undated, (4 folders) (Box 9 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of art works by Lydia Field Emmet (see also sol 11), undated, (12 folders) (Box 10 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of art works by Jane Emmet De Glehn (see also sol 11), undated (Box 10 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of art works by Bay (Ellen) Emmet, undated (Box 10 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of art works by Rosamond Sherwood (see also sol 11), undated (Box 10 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of art works by Wilfrid De Glehn, undated (Box 11 (sol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of portrait of Louis Metcalfe Kobbe by Marie O. Kobbe, undated (Box 10 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of portrait of Jane Emmet De Glehn by John Singer Sargent, undated (Box 10 (hol), Reel 4766)
  - Photographs of Emmet Family exhibition, Alderson Gallery, NY, 1936 (Box 11 (sol), Reel 4766)
- Audiovisual Material, 1988, Series 12:; (box 10, 1 folder)
  The file contains a videotape biography of the artistic accomplishments of the Emmet family.
  - Videotape: The Emmets: Portrait of a Family by Nancy B. Doyle, 1988 (Box 10 (hol), Reel unfilmed)
- Artifacts, undated, Series 13:; (box 10, 2 folders)
  The files contain three-dimensional items which are not directly related to other series.
  - Rear-view optical device, undated (Box 10 (hol), Reel unfilmed)
  - Locks of hair from family members, undated (Box 10 (hol), Reel unfilmed)